50 two years later, there's a knock on the door.
Et deux ans plus tard, on frappe àla porte.
Guy opens it, and there is the snail...
Le gars ouvre et c'est l'escargot
...who says, "What the heck was all that about?"
qui lui sort : "Pourquoi t'as fait ça ?"
I don't really get it.
Je comprends pas.
Well, see, it took two years for the snail to--
Parce qu'en fait, l'escargot a mis deux ans à...
Not important.
Aucune importance.
-Can I ask you a question? -Sure.
- Je peux te demander un truc ? - Oui.
Where do you think this is going?
Jusqu'où va-t-on aller ?
To be honest, I was hoping at least second base.
J'espérais aller au moins jusqu'au pelotage.
You're so funny.
Tu es si drôle!
You're like a standup comedian.
On dirait un humoriste!
A Jewish standup comedian, that would be new.
Un humoriste juif, quelle surprise!
Actually, I think a lot of them are Jewish.
En fait, je crois qu‘il y a beaucoup d'humoristes juifs.
No, l was just-- Because-- Never mind.
Justement je disais ça parce que… Laisse tomber.
Look, Howard, this is our third date, and we both know what that means.
Howard, c‘est notre troisième rencard et on sait bien ce que ça veut dire.
-We do? -Sex.
- Vraiment ? - Du sexe.
You're kidding.
C‘est pas vrai !
But I need to know whether you're looking for a relationship...
Il faut que je sache si tu cherches une relation sérieuse
...or a one-night stand.
ou une aventure d'un soir.
Okay, just to be clear, there's only one correct answer, right?
Il n‘y a qu'une seule bonne réponse, pas vrai ?
I mean, it's not like "Chicken or fish?" on an airplane?
C‘est pas comme le ”poulet ou poisson" en avion ?
Maybe you need to think about it a little.
Tu devrais peut-être y réfléchir.
Well, you know, it's not unheard of...
Tu sais, on a déjà vu
...for a one-night stand to turn into a relationship.
une aventure d'un soir devenir une vraie relation.
Call me when you figure it out.
Appelle—moi quand tu sauras.
Three dates means sex?
Trois rencards et on couche ?
Who knew?
Qui l'eût cru ?
Greetings, homeys.
Salut, les mecs.
Homette.
Et la miss...
Why are you back from your date so early?
Pourquoi tu rentres sitôt?
Well, in romance, as in show business, always leave them wanting more.
En amour comme en affaires, il faut savoir se faire désirer.
-What exactly does that mean? -He struck out.
- Ça veut dire quoi ? - Il a merdé.
Hey, did you know that three dates with the same woman...
Vous saviez qu'au bout de trois rencards,
...is the threshold for sex?
on peut coucher avec une fille ?
Actually, I've never had three dates with the same woman.
En fait, j'ai jamais eu trois rencards avec une fille.
With Penny and me, it took two years.
Penny et moi, il nous a fallu deux ans.
But now that I think about it, that was three dates.
Mais tout bien réfléchi, c‘est vrai que ça faisait trois rencards.
Okay, well, before you and Penny hooked up...
Avant de conclure avec Penny,
...did she ask for any kind of commitment?
est-ce qu'elle t‘a parlé d'engagement ?
No, she was pretty clear about wanting to keep her options open.
Non, elle voulait clairement être libre d‘aller voir ailleurs.
l have something to announce, but out of respect for convention...
J'ai une annonce à faire, mais par respect des conventions,
...I will wait for you to finish your conversation.
j‘attendrai la fin de cette conversation.
What are you talking about?
De quoi parlez-vous ?
The cultural paradigm in which people have sex after three dates.
Du paradigme culturel impliquant le sexe après trois rencards.
Now, are we talking "date" the social interaction...
Par ”rencard", on parle bien de rendez—vous,
...or "date" the dried fruit?
pas de renseignement ?
Never mind. What's your announcement?
Oublié. Alors, ton annonce ?
SHELDON: Oh, good, my turn.
Super, mon tour.
Well, this is very exciting, and I wanted you to be among the first to know--
C‘est très palpitant. Je voulais que vous sachiez en premier...
I hear you're gonna be on the radio...
Hé, tu vas passer àla radio
...with Ira Flatow from Science Friday next week.
dans l'émission d'lra Flatow, Science Friday ?
Thank you, Kripke...
Merci Kripke,
...for depriving me of the opportunity to share my news with my friends.
tu Viens de me priver de l'occasion de l'annoncer à mes amis.
My pleasure.
De rien.
-My thank-you was not sincere. -But my pleasure is.
- Mon ”merci" n‘avait rien de sincère. - Mais moi, je l'étais.
Let me ask you a question.
Je peux te demander
At what point did National Public Radio...
depuis quand National Public Radio
...have to start scraping the bottom of the barrel for its guests?
est obligé de racler les fonds de tiroir pour trouver un invité ?
Eeh-eeh. Don't answer. It's rhetorical.
Ne réponds pas. C‘est rhétorique.
Well, why are you such a stupidhead?
Pourquoi es-tu si bête ?
That is also rhetorical.
C‘est rhétorique, ça aussi.
I'm sorry you had to hear that.
Navré de vous avoir infligé ça.
Are you really gonna be on NPR?
Tu vas vraiment passer sur NPR ?
Yes, they're interviewing me by phone from my office...
Oui. Entretien téléphonique depuis mon bureau
...regarding the recent so-called discovery of magnetic monopoles in spin ices.
sur la "découverte" de monopôles magnétiques dans les glaces de spin.
It's pledge week, and they're trying to goose the ratings with controversy.
C‘est la semaine des dons, ils veulent doper l‘audimat avec une polémique.
-Very cool. Congratulations. -Thank you. My mother is very excited.
- C‘est super. Félicitations. - Merci. Ma mère est folle de joie.
She's convening her Bible study group to listen in...
Elle a invité son groupe d‘étude biblique
...and then pray for my soul.
à m‘écouter et à prier pour mon âme.
l was on the radio once.
J'ai déjà appelé
I called into Fever 104 FM New Delhi...
Fever 104 FM New Delhi, une fois,
...and was the fourth person to say the phrase that pays:
etj'ai été la 4e personne à dire la phrase qui tue...
That means "Fever 104: Home of the really good current music."
Ce qui veut dire : "Fever 104: c‘est ici, la bonne musique actuelle."
It's much catchier in Hindi.
Ça sonne mieux en hindi.
All right, these are the talking points for my NPR interview tomorrow.
Bien, alors voilà les sujets que j‘aborderai pendant mon entretien sur NPR demain.
I need to make sure they're simple enough...
Il faut que ce soit compréhensible,
...for the less educated in the audience to understand.
pour que les auditeurs les moins instruits comprennent.
Howard, look this over and tell me what's unclear to you.
Howard, jette un œil et dis—moi ce qui t'échappe.
l have a Master's in engineering from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology.
J'ai un master en ingénierie du Massachusetts Institute of Technology.
It required the completion of 144 units of grad work and an original thesis.
Il nécessite la validation de 144 crédits et une thèse originale.
Yes.
Oui.
Look this over and tell me what's unclear to you.
jette un œil et dis—moi ce qui t'échappe.
You know, when Sheldon gives you homework, you don't have to do it.
Si Sheldon te donne des devoirs, t'es pas obligé de les faire.
In fact, it's better if you don't. Otherwise, the rest of us look bad.
D‘ailleurs, ne les fais pas. Sinon, on a l‘air paresseux.
-Hi, guys. -Hello.
- Salut, les gars. - Salut.
Yo, Raj, talk to me.
Raj, parle-moi.
I'm sorry, just screwing with you.
Mais non, je te taquine !
Hey, Howard, why haven't you called Bernadette?
Pourquoi t'as pas appelé Bernadette ?
Did she say something?
Elle t‘a parlé ?
Said she hasn't heard from you. I thought you liked her.
Une semaine sans nouvelles, t'as pas accroché ?
I do, you know, but she wants a commitment...
Si, mais elle veut que je m'engage
...and I'm not sure she's my type.
etje suis pas sûr qu'elle soit mon type.
She agreed to go out with you for free. What more do you need?
Elle sort avec toi gratuitement. Tu veux quoi de plus ?
Look, Bernadette is really nice.
Bernadette est très gentille...
I just always thought when I finally settled down into a relationship...
mais j'ai toujours pensé que quand je me rangerais,
...it would be with someone, you know, different.
ce serait avec quelqu'un de... différent.
Different how?
Différente comment ?
Well, you know, more like Megan Fox from Transformers...
Tu sais, plus comme Megan Fox dans Transformers
...or Katee Sackhoff from Battlestar Galactica.
ou Katee Sackhoff, de Battlestar Galactica.
Are you high?
T'as fumé ou quoi ?
You'd have a better shot with the three-breasted Martian from Total Recall.
T'aurais plus de chances avec la martienne à trois seins de Total Recall.
Okay, now you're just being unrealistic. Anyway, that movie was 20 years ago.
Ça, c‘est pas du tout réaliste. En plus, ce film a 20 ans.
Imagine how saggy those things would be.
Elle doit sûrement avoir les seins qui tombent.
You're gonna throw away a great girl like Bernadette...
Tu vas jeter une chic fille comme Bernadette
...because you're holding out for some fantasy?
pour t‘accrocher à un fantasme ridicule ?
Hey, just because you settled doesn't mean I have to.
Le fait que tu te sois casée ne m'oblige pas à l‘être aussi!
Excuse me, I'm sitting here.
Pardon, je suis la.
Hey, I did not settle for Leonard.
Hé, je me suis pas ”casée" avec lui.
I mean, obviously, he isn't the kind of guy I usually go outwith.
Bon, c‘est sûr que j'ai pas l'habitude de sortir avec ce genre de mecs...
You know, physically.
physiquement, je parle.
Again, I'm right here.
Je suis la, bis.
I do notjudge a book by its cover. lam interested in the person underneath.
L'habit ne fait pas le moine. Je m‘intéresse àla beauté intérieure.
lam here, right? You see me?
Je suis la, ohé ! Vous me voyez ?
Hey, I'm interested in what's inside people too.
Moi aussi, je m‘intéresse àla beauté intérieure,
But, you know, why is it wrong to want those insides wrapped up...
mais quel mal y a-t-il à vouloir enrober cette beauté
...in, say, the delicious caramel that is Halle Berry?
dans un délicieux caramel, comme Halle Berry ?
Yes, you're delicious caramel too.
Oui, toi aussi, tu es un délicieux caramel.
I will tell you why it's wrong--
Je vais te dire où est le mai.
-Excuse me, may I interject? -What?
- Pardon, puis-je intervenir ? - Quoi ?
Biologically speaking, Howard is perfectlyjustified...
Sur le plan biologique, Howard a parfaitement raison
...in seeking out the optimum mate for the propagation of his genetic line.
de chercher une partenaire optimale pour perpétuer sa descendance.
Thank you, Sheldon.
Merci, Sheldon.
Whether that propagation is in the interest of humanity...
En revanche, est-ce dans l‘intérêt de l'humanité ?
...is an entirely different question.
Voilà une toute autre question.
IRA [OVER RADIO]: This is Ira Flatow and you're listening to NPR'S Science Friday.
Je suis [la Flatow et vous écoutez Science Friday sur NPR.
Joining us today by phone from his office in Pasadena, California...
En direct par téléphone depuis son bureau de Pasadena,
...is Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
retrouvons le Dr Sheldon Cooper.
Oh, this is gonna be a riot.
Ça va être énorme!
Thanks for being with us today, Dr. Cooper.
Merci d'être avec nous, Dr Cooper.
My pleasure, Ira.
Je suis ravi, lra.
Now, let's talk about magnetic monopoles.
Parlons un peu des monopôles magnétiques.
Can you explain to our audience just what a monopole is?
Pouvez-vous expliquer à nos auditeurs ce qu'est un monopôle ?
Of course.
Bien sûr.
First, consider an ordinary magnet, which has, as even the most uneducated...
Examinons tout d‘abord un aimant ordinaire qui a,
...two poles...
deux pôles :
...a north and south pole.
un pôle nord et un pôle sud.
If you cut that in half, you have two smaller magnets...
Coupez-Ie en deux et vous obtiendrez deux petits aimants,
...each with its own north and south pole.
possédant chacun ses propres pôles nord et sud.
Dr. Cooper, I think there might be something wrong with our connection.
Dr Cooper, je crois que nous avons un problème technique.
No, I hear you fine.
Non, je vous entends très bien.
As I was saying, an ordinary magnet has two poles.
Comme je le disais, un aimant ordinaire possède deux pôles.
The primary characteristic of a monopole...
La caractéristique d'un monopôle,
...is that it has only one pole, hence, "monopole."
c‘est de ne posséder qu'un seul pôle, d'où le nom de "monopôle".
SHELDON: A requirement for string theory, or M-theory, if you will...
La théorie des cordes ou théorie M, si vous préférez,
...is the existence of such monopoles.
est fondée sur l'existence de ces monopôles.
Imyself led an expedition to the Arctic Circle in search of said particles.
J‘ai mené une expédition au cercle Arctique pour en trouver...
Kripke, I found the nozzle. I'm going to kill you.
Kripke, j'ai vu le tuyau, je vais te tuer!
So nice you could join me this evening. You're looking lovely as always.
Merci d‘avoir pu te joindre à moi. Tu es ravissante, comme toujours.
Thanks, Howard.
Merci, Howard.
Always nice to be part of your masturbatory fantasies.
C‘est un plaisir d'être dans ton fantasme masturbatoire.
Come on, Katee, don't make it sound so cheap.
Arrête, Katee. Ce n‘est pas si dégradant que ça.
I'm sorry. Fiddling with yourself in the bathtub is a real class act.
Désolé. Se tripoter dans sa baignoire est vraiment très classe.
Thank you.
Merci.
So, ahem, shall we get started?
Alors, on commence ?
Sure, but can I ask you a question first?
Je peux te poser une question, avant ?
You wanna play Cylon and colonist?
Tu veux jouer au Cylon et au colon ?
No, I wanna know why you're playing make-believe with me...
Pourquoi préfères-tu fantasmer sur moi
...when you could be out with a real woman tonight.
plutôt que de sortir avec une vraie femme ?
-You mean Bernadette? -No, I mean Princess Leia.
- Tu parles de Bernadette ? - Non, de la Princesse Leia.
Of course I mean Bernadette.
Évidemment, Bernadette.
She's a wonderful girl and she really likes you.
C‘est une fille géniale qui t'aime beaucoup.
-I know, but she's not you. -l'm not me.
- Oui, mais elle n‘est pas comme toi. - Je n'existe pas.
The real me is in Beverly Hills with a tall, handsome rich guy.
La vraie moi est à Beverly Hills avec un mec grand et riche.
-Really? Tall? -Six-four.
- Grand, vraiment ? - 1,95 m.
You've got a wonderful girl in your life, and you're ignoring her...
Tu connais cette fille merveilleuse et tu l‘ignores
...to spend your nights in the bathtub with a mental image and a washcloth.
pour passer des soirées dans ton bain avec un fantasme et un gant de toilette.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Howard!
Howard !
What are you doing in there?
Qu'est—ce que tu fous là-dedans ?
I'm taking a bath!
Je prends un bain!
I hope that's all you're doing! We share that tub!
J'espère que c‘est tout! On la partage, cette baignoire!
Don't remind me!
Pas besoin de me le rappeler!
All soaped up and no place to go.
Je suis tout propre et ça ne sert à rien.
How you doing, buddy?
Comment ça va ?
l was humiliated on national radio. How do you think I'm doing?
J'ai été humilié sur une radio nationale. A ton avis ?
Come on, it wasn't that bad.
C‘était pas si terrible.
What do you want?
Qu'y a-t-il ?
[IN MUNCHKIN VOICE] We represent the Lollipop Guild, and we want you.
On fait partie de la chorale de castrats et on veut que tu nous rejoignes !
-Okay, so Kripke played ajoke on you. -It wasn't funny.
- Kripke t‘a fait une farce. - C‘était pas drôle.
[IN NORMAL VOICE] I thought it was funny.
- J'ai trouvé ça drôle. - Raj !
Did you laugh?
Tu as rigolé ?
I fell on the floor.
J'en suis tombé par terre.
All right, he got you. You can get him back.
Il t‘ajoué un tour. Tu peux lui rendre la pareille.
-I refuse to sink to his level. -You can't sink.
- Je ne m'abaisserai pas à son niveau. - Impossible.
With all that helium in you, you're lucky you don't float away.
Avec tout l'hélium que t'as inhalé, t'es chanceux de ne pas t'envoler.
Are you really admitting defeat?
Tu vas admettre ta défaite ?
-I never admit defeat. -Good.
- Jamais. - Bien.
However, on an unrelated topic, I'm never getting out of this bed again.
Cependant, sur un tout autre sujet, je ne quitterai plus jamais mon lit.
What if you could make Kripke look even sillier than he made you look?
Et si tu pouvais ridiculiser Kripke plus qu'il ne t‘a ridiculisé ?
-I don't think that's possible. -You're not helping.
- C‘est impossible. - Tu aides pas, la !
I didn't come to help. I came to mock.
Je suis pas venu aider, je suis venu me moquer!
Sheldon, what you need to do...
Sheldon, tu dois trouver
...is figure out a way to exact vengeance on Kripke, like....
un moyen de te venger de Kripke, comme par exemple...
Like how the Joker got back at Batman...
quand le Joker se venge de Batman
...for putting him in the Arkham Asylum for the Criminally Insane.
pour l‘avoir enfermé dans l‘asile d‘Arkham.
He didn't stay and talk about his feelings with the other villains.
Il est pas resté papoter avec les autres méchants,
He broke out and poisoned Gotham's water supply.
il s‘est évadé pour empoisonner l‘eau de Gotham.
Well...
En effet...
...I suppose I could poison Kripke.
je pourrais l'empoisonner.
-No, no. SHELDON: It's a simple matter.
- Non ! - C‘est pas compliqué,
There are several toxic chemicals that would be untraceable in an autopsy.
Il existe des composés toxiques indétectables lors d‘une autopsie.
Okay, that's the spirit...
Bon, tu as compris l‘idée,
...but let's dial it back to a nonlethal form of vengeance.
mais tâchons de trouver une vengeance moins mortelle.
How about we put a whoopee cushion on his office chair?
Pourquoi pas un coussin péteur sur sa chaise ?
He'll sit down and it'll sound like he's flatulent even though he's not.
Il aura l‘air d‘avoir des flatulences alors qu'en fait, non.
Let's keep thinking.
Continuons de réfléchir.
Oh, gee, you're too late.
T‘arrives trop tard.
Scarlett Johansson and Wonder Woman were here...
Scarlett Johansson et Wonder Woman
...trolling around for neurotic little weasels.
cherchaient justement une petite fouine.
I came to talk to Bernadette. She's working today, right?
Je suis venu parler à Bernadette. Elle travaille, non ?
-I don't think she wants to see you. -Why not?
- Oui, mais elle ne veut pas te voir. - Pourquoi ?
Come on. You hurt her feelings by not calling her all week.
Tu ne l'as pas rappelée, elle est blessée!
Plus, I've been kind of talking some smack about you.
En plus, je lui ai dit du mal de toi.
-Hello, Howard. -Wait, Bernadette, I need to talk to you.
- Salut, Howard. - Attends, Bernadette. Je dois te parler.
-I can't. I'm working. -This will only take a second.
- Je peux pas, je travaille. - Ce sera bref.
You asked me to think about where our relationship was going...
Tu voulais que je réfléchisse à notre relation
...and I did.
et c‘est ce que j'ai fait.
Bernadette...
Bernadette,
...will you marry me?
veux-tu m‘épouser ?
Is this more comedy that I don't understand?
C‘est encore une blague que je ne comprends pas ?
No, I'm serious.
Non, je suis très sérieux.
I'm never gonna find another girl like you...
Je retrouverai jamais une fille comme toi,
...who likes me and is, you know, real.
qui tient à moi et qui est... réelle.
-So this isn't a joke? -No.
- Donc tu ne plaisantes pas ? - Non.
Then you're insane.
Alors tu es cinglé.
I prefer to think of myself as quirky.
Je préfère le terme "excentrique".
Howard, we've only been on three dates. We haven't even had sex yet.
On est sortis ensemble trois fois. On n‘a pas encore couché ensemble.
Fair enough. When's your break?
Je vois. A quelle heure est ta pause ?
Don't you just hate when this happens?
C‘est la honte quand ça arrive, hein ?
All right, how's this for revenge?
Que dites-vous de ça pour une vengeance ?
A solution of hydrogen peroxide and one of saturated potassium iodide.
Une solution de peroxyde d‘hydrogène et une d'iodure de potassium saturée.
-What's this? -Mountain Dew.
- Et c‘est quoi, ça ? - Un soda.
Ah. Refreshing.
Rafraîchissant.
Now, we're going to combine these chemicals with ordinary dish soap...
Nous allons mélanger ces solutions à du savon ordinaire,
...creating a little exothermic release of oxygen.
créant ainsi une réaction exothermique d'oxygène.
-Foamy vengeance. -Yes, exactly.
- Une vengeance mousseuse... - Exactement.
This is brilliant, Sheldon.
C‘est brillant, Sheldon.
How are we gonna deploy it in Kripke's office?
Comment mettre ça dans son bureau ?
Already taken care of. Observe.
Je m'en suis déjà occupé. Regardez.
This is a live shot of Kripke's lab via a mini webcam l was able to install...
Nous voici dans le labo de Kripke grâce à une mini Webcam que j'ai pu installer
...thanks to a dollar bill discreetly placed in the nightjanitor's shirt pocket.
grâce à un dollar glissé dans la poche de l‘homme de ménage.
At the same time, I also secured large quantities of these chemicals...
J'ai également placé plusieurs litres de ces solutions
...above the tiles in the drop ceiling.
dans son faux plafond.
Sheldon, you remind me of a young Lex Luthor.
Sheldon, tu me rappelles Lex Luthor, dans sajeunesse.
You flatter me, sir.
Vous me flattez, mon cher.
-Let me guess, motion sensors? -Yes.
- Détecteurs de mouvements ? - Oui.
The reaction will be triggered when Kripke reaches the center of the room.
Le processus se déclenchera quand Kripke sera au centre dela pièce.
I gotta say, I am really impressed.
Je suis vraiment impressionné.
This is truly the Sheldon Cooper way to get even.
Voilà une vraie vengeance àla Sheldon.
It may be low-tech...
Assez basique,
...but I still maintain the whoopee cushion has comic validity.
mais je soutiens la valeur comique du coussin péteur.
Here comes Kripke.
Tiens, voilà Kripke.
LEONARD: Who's that with him?
Qui est avec lui ?
RAJESH: I believe that's the president of the university.
On dirait le président de l‘université.
-The board of directors. Abort! Abort! -There is no abort.
- Et le comité ! On abandonne! - Impossible...
-How could you not put in an abort? -I made a boo-boo, all right?
- Y a pas moyen d'abandonner ? - J'ai fait une bévue, d'accord ?
I think the board will really appreciate how well we're using that NSA grant.
Le comité appréciera la façon dont les fonds de la NSA ont été utilisés.
Right here we have a micro-controlled plasma--
Ici, nous avons un plasma microcontrôlé...
At least they don't know it was you.
Ils ne savent pas que c‘est toi.
SHELDON [OVER COMPUTER]: Hello, Kripke.
Bonjour, Kripke.
This classic prank comes to you...
Je te retourne la pareille,
...from the malevolent mind of Sheldon Cooper.
de la part de l'esprit diabolique de Sheldon Cooper.
Ifyou'd like to see the look on your stupid face...
Si tu veux voir l'air stupide sur ta face,
...this Video is being instantly uploaded to YouTube.
cette Vidéo a été envoyée instantanément sur YouTube.
Oh, and a hat tip to Leonard Hofstadter and Raj Koothrappali...
Et merci & Leonard Hofstadter et Raj Koothrappali
...for their support and encouragement in this enterprise.
qui m'ont soutenu et encouragé dans cette entreprise.
Well, I'm going back to India. What's your plan?
Moi, je rentre en Inde. Et toi ?
-Hey, here's your tip from Table 7. -Oh, thanks.
- Tiens, Ie pourboire de la table 7. - Merci.
Oh, now what?
Quoi, encore ?
-You want me to throw him out? -No, that's okay.
- Je le mets dehors ? - Non, ça ira.
Are you sure? He's small.
Tu en es sûre ? Il est petit.
Bet I could get a nice tight spiral on him.
Je peux le mettre K.O. en lui lançant un objet.
I wanna dedicate this number to a great gal who I've done wrong.
J'aimerais dédicacer cette chanson à une chouette fille que j'ai blessée.
[SINGING] Bernadette
Bernadette
I am so sorry For trying to propose to you
Je suis désolé d‘avoir demandé ta main
Bernadette
Bernadette
You found it creepy But that's just the kind of thing I do
ça t'a fait flipper Mais je suis comme ça, j'y peux rien
[know now it was too soon To talk of love
J'ai compris que parler d‘amour trop tôt C‘est pas bien
It was just a crazy idea That came to me in my tub
C‘était une idée de barjo Qui m'est venue dans mon bain
But, Bernadette Give me one more chance
Mais Bernadette Donne-moi une autre chance
Sweet Bernadette
Douce Bernadette
I'll get the hang of this thing They call romance
Un jour, promis j'y arriverai
[dream to once again Kiss your lips
Tes lèvres & nouveau, je les embrasserai
Sweet Bernadette
Douce Bernadette
Sincerely yours, Howard Wolowitz
Cordialement, Howard Wolowitz
Bernadette
Bernadette
Oh, I am so sorry.
Je suis sincèrement désolée.
Are you kidding?
Tu rigoles ?
That's the most romantic thing anyone's ever done for me.
J'ai jamais rien eu d‘aussi romantique!
Bernadette
Bernadette
Thank you, Cheesecake Factory.
Merci, Cheesecake Factory!
[ENGLISH - US - SDH]
[FRENCH]